

Ganavi P Graphic Designer

working with an organization gives us vast experience living in the corporate world with our colleagues as well as to do work in a team, divide the work to each member so that every member will learn something new everyday at every task, how to deal with different situations or problems to find out the solution for it..... working organization's and motivates to take a new challenges and work upon it.

Mobile +91 7676994875



E-mail gowdagana143@gmail.com

Behance https://www.behance.net/ganavipapu

in

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/ganavi-p-647037240

SKILLS



Adobe Illustrator











WORK EXPERIENCE

andaz press°

2019-2021 Graphic Designer

ANDAZ INFOTECH PVT. LTD. - July 2019 - 2021

Enhancing creative ideas in the form of user-centricity and making them presentable according to the niche of the user and software firms Solving challenging design problems and providing good collateral for clients.



2021-2023 **Graphic Designer**

BYJU'S Edu-Tech Company. - November 2021 - 2023

Enhancing creative ideas in the form of marketing and Make it presentable to enhance the brand of Byjus. solving challenging problems of design and getting Marketing material executed.

EDUCATION

Degree in SJR College Bangalore

2014 - 2017 Regular course

3 Years Regular course

Pre-University Course 2012 - 2014

Hobbies

Reading | Learning a new tools | Carrom | Cooking | Badminton

KNOWLEDGE

Illustration design

Creating images, Web design illustrations, and other graphics

Photoshop

Photo Editing, GIF Animations, Web Ads and Logo Designing

Visual Design Infographics

Brand design

Designing logos icons, and various illustrations

Power Point

Create presentations from scratch or a template and Add text, images, art, and videos.